Srila Guru Maharaj
当 Guru maharaj
when he was speaking about Giriraj Govardhan
谈到 哥尔丹山 （Giriraj Govardhan）
the Govardhan Shila  he said:
他说
“His position is similar to Mahaprabhu”.
他(哥尔丹山）所在的立场和玛哈帕布很像
Jiva Goswami
Jiva goswami
in describing Chaitanya Mahaprabhu he says:
这样形容 柴坦亚 玛哈帕布：
“Internally Krishna, externally as Gaura,
内在是krishna,外表是Gaura(柴坦亚玛哈帕布）
internally Krishna, externally in the mood of the servitor”.
他的内心是krishna,外在是仆人的心态
Even the person in this world
甚至在这个世界的人
can simultaneously hold different identities,
能同时持有不同的身份
like a girl can be a daughter,
就像女孩，可以是女儿
a sister, a mother, a wife.
是妹妹，母亲，妻子
She can hold those positions all simultaneously.
她可以同时拥有这些身份
From one group, or one perspective,
从一个圈子，或者一个角度
the sister, the mother, the wife, the daughter –
姐妹，母亲，妻子，女儿
it is all possible.
这都是可能的
So that Krishna
所以，Krishna
in all of his Divine Manifestations
他所有神圣的显现
can hold multiple positions is not intangible?
拥有不同的身份地位难道会令人难以理解吗？
And following the principle of that –
以及，遵循以下的原则
a part of the infinite is the infinite.
无限的一部分也是无限的
So we take one stone from Govardhan Hill
我们从哥尔丹山搬来一块石头
and it’s the whole Govardhan Hill, it is completely Krishna.
他就是整座哥尔丹山，是Krishna完整展现
That is Achintya Shakti, His inconceivable potency.
Achintya Shakti ，他不可思议的力量
Yet, sometimes Radha Khunda is considered
有时，Radha（茹阿达） 湖被当做
the representation of Radharani,
Radharani（茹阿达茹阿妮）的展现
Govardhan - the representation of Krishna,
Govardhan(哥尔丹山)------Krishna的展现
many different things to be considered.
很多事情是被这样考虑的
So in conclusion we will say, achintya beda bed.
所以总的来说，
Or as the Thai people say:
就像泰国人常讲的：
“Same same, but different”.
"看起来一样，实则不同"（同中有异）
Krishna, and devotee of Krishna.
Krishna ，Krishna 的信徒
As Mahaprabhu is Krishna, and devotee of Krishna.
Mahaprabhu 是Krishna 本身，也是他的信徒
But He descended for Bhakta Bhav
但是他的降临是为了Bhakta Bhav
and ultimately Radha Bhav
最终的 Radha Bhav
Bhakta Bhav - devotee of Krishna mentality,
Bhakta Bhav ---- Krishna 的奉爱者的心态
and Radharani - Radha Bhav.
和Radharani ----Radha Bhav
So in this way there is an intimate connection between
这样的方式，包含了一种亲密的关系
Sri Krishna Chaitanya Mahaprabhu and Giriraj Govardhan.
在 Krishna   Chaitanya Mahaprabhu(柴坦亚 玛哈帕布）和哥尔丹山之间